{"qid":1,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Who was the 1st Prime Minister of India?","ans":"Pandit Jawaharlal Nehru","1":"Pandit Jawaharlal Nehru","2":"Lal Bahadur Shastri","3":"Gulzar Lal Nanda","4":"None of the Above"}
{"qid":2,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"The first Women External Affair Minister of India was:","ans":"Indira Gandhi","1":"Sushma Swaraj","2":"Jayalalitha","3":"Pratibha Patil","4":"Indira Gandhi"}
{"qid":3,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Who among the following known as Pocket Hercules?","ans":"Manohar Aich","1":"Mike Tyson","2":"Manohar Aich","3":"Manotosh Roy","4":"Muhammad Ali"}
{"qid":4,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Who is the creator of the Rock Garden in Chandigarh?","ans":"Pupal Jayakar","1":"Mike Tyson","2":"Le Corbousier","3":"Glen","4":"Nek Chand"}
{"qid":5,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Who was known as Iron man of India?","ans":"Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel","1":"Govind Ballabh Pant","2":"Jawaharlal Nehru","3":"Subhash Chandra Bose","4":"Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel"}
{"qid":6,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"The Indian to beat the computers in mathematical wizardry is","ans":"Shakunthala Devi","1":"Ramanujam","2":"Rina Panigrahi","3":"Raja Ramanna","4":"Shakunthala Devi"}
{"qid":7,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Jude Felix is a famous Indian player in which of the fields?","ans":"Hockey","1":"Volleyball","2":"Tennis","3":"Football","4":"Hockey"}
{"qid":8,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Professor Amartya Sen is famous in which of the fields?","ans":"Economics","1":"Electronics","2":"Economics","3":"Geology","4":"Biochemistry"}
{"qid":9,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Which of the following was Satyajit Ray associated with?","ans":"Film Direction","1":"Classical music","2":"Commercial art","3":"Film Direction","4":"Classical dance"}
{"qid":10,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Amjad Ali Khan is associated with which of the following musical instruments?","ans":"Sarod","1":"Veena","2":"Violin","3":"Sitar","4":"Sarod"}
{"qid":11,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Who is known as the 'Lady with the Lamp'?","ans":"Florence Nightingale","1":"Sarojini Naidu","2":"Florence Nightingale","3":"Film Direction","4":"Joan of Arc"}
{"qid":12,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Who is the architect of the world's longest constitution?","ans":"BR Ambedkar","1":"BR Rao","2":"BR Ambedkar","3":"C Rajagoplachari","4":"Jawaharlal Nehru"}
{"qid":13,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Who has become the first Indian woman to scale Mount Everest for the 4th time?","ans":"Anshu Jamsenpa","1":"Anshu Jamsenpa","2":"Arunima Sinha","3":"Baichendri Pal","4":"None of the above"}
{"qid":14,"q_set":"per","type":"Personalities","question":"Who is the black hole man of India?","ans":"Professor Vishweshwara","1":"Professor Singh","2":"Professor Ramayya","3":"Professor Vishweshwara","4":"Professor Ganesan"}
